Let's take a look at this code starting at the top with the very first line,
让我们看看这个开头开头的代码
import turtle. Now what could that mean?
进口乌龟  这意味着什么呢 ?
In English, import means to bring something in from somewhere
在英语中 导入意味着从某处带来某种东西
else like importing cookies from Denmark or coffee from Peru,
比如从丹麦进口饼干或者从秘鲁进口咖啡
and we've heard that turtle is a name for
我们听说海龟是
this imaginary robot that can draw on the screen.
这个假想的机器人可以在屏幕上绘制
So, maybe this line is bringing us a turtle from somewhere.
也许这条线给我们带来了一只乌龟
For now, you probably have no idea where
现在你可能不知道
the turtle is coming from and that's completely okay,
海龟是从那来的完全可以
it's probably not from Peru.
可能不是从秘鲁来的
Next, the story seems to be introducing a character named George.
接下来 故事似乎在介绍一个名叫乔治的人物
The second line says George equals turtle.Turtle.
第二条线说乔治等于龟龟
It kind of sounds like this is saying George is
听起来好像是乔治
equal to a turtle or maybe a double turtle.
等于一只乌龟或者一只双龟
Usually in English, we'd say that George is a turtle.
通常用英语 我们会说乔治是乌龟
Let's experiment with the code and see what we can figure out.
让我们实验一下代码 看看我们能找到什么
Something we can do if we don't know what the code does
如果我们不知道密码是什么
yet is to try changing things and see what happens.
但要试着改变事情看看会发生什么
For instance, there might not be
例如 可能没有
any particular reason this turtle has to be named George.
这只乌龟必须被命名为乔治
Let's try changing the turtle's name from George to something else like Amy.
让我们尝试将乌龟的名字从乔治改变为艾米的其他东西